Six littles souls in search of a little harmony.
Duets is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Bruce Paltrow.
Duets is a road-trip comedy which revolves around the little known world
of karaoke and the whimsical characters who inhabit it.
All roads lead to Omaha, site of a national karaoke competition where this motley
group of singers and stars come together for a blow-out sing-off.
Suzi Loomis, played by Maria Bello.
Reggie Kane, played by Andre Braugher.
Todd Woods, played by Paul Giamatti.
Ricky Dean, played by Huey Lewis.
Liv, played by Gwyneth Paltrow.
Billy, played by Scott Speedman.
Duets is a 2000 American road musical comedy drama film co-produced and
directed by Bruce Paltrow, and written by John Byrum.
The motion picture features an ensemble cast with Gwyneth Paltrow, Huey Lewis, Paul Giamatti,
Maria Bello, Angie Dickinson, Scott Speedman, and Andre Braugher among others.
The movie "revolves around the little known world of karaoke
competitions and the wayward characters who inhabit it."
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.